<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coronavirus App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>


    <string name="next">NÄCHSTER</string>
    <string name="skip">ÜBERSPRINGEN</string>
    <string name="start">ICH HABS</string>

    <string name="intro_1_title">Seien Sie sicher vor \n Coronavirus!</string>
    <string name="intro_1_desc">Reinigen Sie Ihre Hände regelmäßig und gründlich mit einer alkoholbasierten Handmassage oder waschen Sie sie mit Wasser und Seife!</string>

    <string name="intro_2_title">Befolgen Sie alle Sicherheitstipps!</string>
    <string name="intro_2_desc">Hände berühren viele Oberflächen und können Viren aufnehmen. Einmal kontaminiert, können Hände das Virus auf Ihre Augen, Nase oder Mund übertragen. Von dort kann das Virus in Ihren Körper eindringen und Sie krank machen.</string>

    <string name="intro_3_title">Schützen Sie sich vor Krankheit!</string>
    <string name="intro_3_desc">Beim Husten und Niesen Mund und Nase mit gebeugtem Ellbogen oder Gewebe abdecken. Werfen Sie das Gewebe sofort nach Gebrauch in einen geschlossenen Behälter.</string>

    <string name="lets_take_your_test">Machen wir Ihren Test</string>
    <string name="back">Zurück</string>
    <string name="coronavirus">VIRUSKRONE</string>
    <string name="main_page_txt">COVID-19 ist eine neue Krankheit, die Ihre Lunge und Atemwege beeinträchtigen kann.</string>
    <string name="test">Prüfung</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptome</string>
    <string name="infected">Infiziert</string>
    <string name="precautions">Vorsichtsmaßnahmen</string>
    <string name="history">Geschichte</string>
    <string name="report">Bericht</string>
    <string name="our_predictions">Unsere Vorhersagen</string>
    <string name="prediction_note">HINWEIS: Diese Vorhersagen sind nicht endgültig. Wir geben Ihnen nur Ergebnisse auf der Grundlage einiger Symptome, die am häufigsten auftreten, und stimmen sie mit Ihren gegebenen Eingaben überein.</string>
    <string name="no_symptoms_found">Keine Symptome gefunden</string>
    <string name="splash_msg">Crona Virus Statik und Test App</string>
    <string name="statics">Statik</string>
    <string name="locationid">Standort-ID</string>
    <string name="continent_name">Kontinent Name</string>
    <string name="country_name">Ländername</string>
    <string name="province_name">Provinzname</string>
    <string name="current_confirmed_count">Aktuelle bestätigte Anzahl</string>
    <string name="confirmed_count">Bestätigte Anzahl</string>
    <string name="suspected_count">Verdächtiger Graf</string>
    <string name="cured_count">Geheilter Graf</string>
    <string name="dead_count">Toter Graf</string>
    <string name="update_time">Updatezeit</string>
    <string name="symptoms_2">Symptome</string>
    <string name="country">Land</string>
    <string name="yes">JA</string>
    <string name="no">NEIN</string>
    <string name="ferver">Fieber</string>
    <string name="is_you_feeling">Fühlst du dieses Symptom seit 7 Tagen?</string>
    <string name="raini_nose">Laufende Nase</string>
    <string name="dry_cough">Trockener Husten</string>
    <string name="short_breath">Kurzatmigkeit</string>
    <string name="sore_throat">Halsentzündung</string>
    <string name="fatigue">Ermüden</string>
    <string name="headache">Kopfschmerzen</string>
    <string name="chill">Ausruhen</string>
    <string name="nausea_vomiting">Übelkeit oder Erbrechen</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea">Durchfall</string>
    <string name="muscle_pain">Muskelschmerzen oder Gelenkschmerzen</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="result_1">Unfortunately! Accourding to our predictions, your numbers is comming Alarming you should checkup to doctor as soon as COVID-19 possible.</string>
    <string name="result_2">Unfortunately! Accourding to our predictions, we got some symptoms in which some are near to main COVID-19 symptoms but you should checkup to doctor for final COVID-19 report.</string>
    <string name="result_3">Unfortunately! Accourding to our predictions, we got some symptoms but also you should checkup to doctor for final COVID-19 report.</string>
    <string name="result_4">Congratulations! Accourding to our predictions, your numbers is comming Normal but also you should checkup to doctor for final COVID-19 report.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_recong">\"RECOGNISING THE SYMPTOMS \"</string>
    <string name="day_1">DAY 1-3</string>
    <string name="symptoms_similar">•\tSymptoms similar to colds.</string>
    <string name="mild_throat">•\tMild throat pain.</string>
    <string name="not_fever">•\tNo fever, not tired.  Still consume food and drink as normal.</string>
    <string name="throat_little">•\tThroat little bit painful, body feels like drunk.</string>
    <string name="voice_becoming">•\tVoice becoming sore.</string>
    <string name="body_temp">•\tBody temperature around 36.5°.</string>
    <string name="beginning_of_dist">•\tBeginning of disturbance on eating habit.</string>
    <string name="mild_headaches">•\t5.Mild headaches</string>
    <string name="mild_diarrhoea">•\tMild diarrhoea</string>
    <string name="day_4">DAY 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">DAY 5</string>
    <string name="throat_pain_and">•\tThroat pain and sore voice</string>
    <string name="mild_body_temp">•\tMild body temp. Body temperature btw 36.5°-36.7°.</string>
    <string name="weak_body_and">•\tWeak body and feeling joints pain.</string>
    <string name="day_6">DAY 6</string>
    <string name="beginning_of_mild">•\tBeginning of mild fever with temperature around 37°</string>
    <string name="dry_cough_1">•\tDry cough</string>
    <string name="throat_pain_while">•\tThroat pain while eating,  swallowing food or talking.</string>
    <string name="exhausted_and_nausea">•\tExhausted and nausea</string>
    <string name="difficulty_in">•\tDifficulty in breathing occasionally</string>
    <string name="fingers_feeling">•\tFingers feeling pain</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_and">•\tDiarrhea and vommitting</string>
    <string name="day_7">DAY 7</string>
    <string name="higher_fever">•\tHigher fever from 37.4°-37.8°</string>
    <string name="couging">•\tCoughing incessantly  with phlegm.</string>
    <string name="body_pain_headache">•\tBody pain and headache.</string>
    <string name="worsening">•\tWorsening diarrhea.</string>
    <string name="vomiting">•\tVomiting</string>
    <string name="day_8">DAY 8</string>
    <string name="fever_arround">•\tFever around 38° or above 38°</string>
    <string name="breathing_difficul">•\tBreathing difficulties, everytime breathing, chest feels heavy.</string>
    <string name="coughing">•\tCoughing incessantly.</string>
    <string name="headaches_joints">•\tHeadaches, joints becoming lame and buttock pain.</string>
    <string name="day_9">DAY 9.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_remain">•\tSymptoms remain unchanged but becoming worst</string>
    <string name="worsening_fever">•\tWorsening fever</string>
    <string name="worsening_cough">•\t3.Worsening cough</string>
    <string name="difficult_breath">•\tDifficulties in breathing and have to struggle hard to breath.</string>
    <string name="what_to_do">What To Do if You Are Sick</string>
    <string name="steps_to_help">Steps to help prevent the spread of COVID-19 if you are sick</string>
    <string name="stay_home">Stay home except to get medical care</string>
    <string name="stay_home_2">•\tStay home: Stay home: People who are mildly ill with COVID-19 are able to isolate at home during their illness. You should restrict activities outside your home, except for getting medical care.</string>
    <string name="avoid_public">•\tAvoid public areas: Do not go to work, school, or public areas.</string>
    <string name="avoid_public_trans">•\tAvoid public transportation: Avoid using public transportation, ride-sharing, or taxis.</string>
    <string name="separate_yourself">Separate yourself from other people and animals in your home</string>
    <string name="stay_away_from">•\tStay away from others: As much as possible, you should stay in a specific room and away from other people in your home. Also, you should use a separate bathroom, if available.</string>
    <string name="limit_contact"><![CDATA[•\tLimit contact with pets & animals: You should restrict contact with pets and other animals while you are sick with COVID-19, just like you would around other people. Although there have not been reports of pets or other animals becoming sick with COVID-19, it is still recommended that people sick with COVID-19 limit contact with animals until more information is known about the virus.]]></string>
    <string name="when_possible">•\tWhen possible, have another member of your household care for your animals while you are sick. If you are sick with COVID-19, avoid contact with your pet, including petting, snuggling, being kissed or licked and sharing food. If you must care for your pet or be around animals while you are sick, wash your hands before and after you interact with pets and wear a facemask. See COVID-19 and Animals for more information.</string>
    <string name="call_ahead">Call ahead before visiting your doctor</string>
    <string name="call_ahead_2">•\tCall ahead: If you have a medical appointment, call the healthcare provider and tell them that you have or may have COVID-19. This will help the healthcare provider’s office take steps to keep other people from getting infected or exposed.</string>
    <string name="wear_a_facemask">Wear a facemask if you are sick</string>
    <string name="if_you_are_sick">•\tIf you are sick: You should wear a facemask when you are around other people (e.g., sharing a room or vehicle) or pets and before you enter a healthcare provider’s office.</string>
    <string name="if_you_are_caring">•\tIf you are caring for others: If the person who is sick is not able to wear a facemask (for example, because it causes trouble breathing), then people who live with the person who is sick should not stay in the same room with them, or they should wear a facemask if they enter a room with the person who is sick.</string>
    <string name="cover_your_coughs">Cover your coughs and sneezes</string>
    <string name="cover_cover">•\tCover: Cover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze.</string>
    <string name="dispose">•\tDispose: Throw used tissues in a lined trash can.</string>
    <string name="wash_hands">•\tWash hands: Immediately wash your hands with soap and water for at least 20 seconds or, if soap and water are not available, clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand sanitizer that contains at least 60% alcohol.</string>
    <string name="clean_your_hands">Clean your hands often</string>
    <string name="wash_hands_2">•\tWash hands: Wash your hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds, especially after blowing your nose, coughing, or sneezing; going to the bathroom; and before eating or preparing food.</string>
    <string name="hand_sanitizer">•\tHand sanitizer: If soap and water are not readily available, use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer with at least 60% alcohol, covering all surfaces of your hands and rubbing them together until they feel dry.</string>
    <string name="soap_and_water">•\tSoap and water: Soap and water are the best option if hands are visibly dirty.</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching">•\tAvoid touching: Avoid touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands.</string>
    <string name="avoid_sharing">Avoid sharing personal household items</string>
    <string name="do_not_share">•\tDo not share: You should not share dishes, drinking glasses, cups, eating utensils, towels, or bedding with other people or pets in your home.</string>
    <string name="wash_throughly">•\tWash thoroughly after use: After using these items, they should be washed thoroughly with soap and water.</string>
    <string name="clean_all">Clean all “high-touch” surfaces everyday</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect">•\tClean and disinfect: Practice routine cleaning of high touch surfaces.</string>
    <string name="high_touch">•\tHigh touch surfaces include counters, tabletops, doorknobs, bathroom fixtures, toilets, phones, keyboards, tablets, and bedside tables.</string>
    <string name="disinfect">•\tDisinfect areas with bodily fluids: Also, clean any surfaces that may have blood, stool, or body fluids on them.</string>
    <string name="household">•\tHousehold cleaners: Use a household cleaning spray or wipe, according to the label instructions. Labels contain instructions for safe and effective use of the cleaning product including precautions you should take when applying the product, such as wearing gloves and making sure you have good ventilation during use of the product.</string>
    <string name="minitor_your_sym">Monitor your symptoms</string>
    <string name="seek_medical">•\tSeek medical attention: Seek prompt medical attention if your illness is worsening (e.g., difficulty breathing).</string>
    <string name="call_your_doc">•\tCall your doctor: Before seeking care, call your healthcare provider and tell them that you have, or are being evaluated for, COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="wear_a_facemask_2">•\tWear a facemask when sick: Put on a facemask before you enter the facility. These steps will help the healthcare provider’s office to keep other people in the office or waiting room from getting infected or exposed.</string>
    <string name="alert_health">•\tAlert health department: Ask your healthcare provider to call the local or state health department. Persons who are placed under active monitoring or facilitated self-monitoring should follow instructions provided by their local health department or occupational health professionals, as appropriate.</string>
    <string name="steps_to_protect">Steps to protect yourself</string>
    <string name="clean_hands">Clean your hands often</string>
    <string name="wash_hands_3">•\tWash your hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds especially after you have been in a public place, or after blowing your nose, coughing, or sneezing.</string>
    <string name="soap_water">•\tIf soap and water are not readily available, use a hand sanitizer that contains at least 60% alcohol. Cover all surfaces of your hands and rub them together until they feel dry.</string>
    <string name="touchings">•\tAvoid touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands.</string>
    <string name="avoid_close">Avoid close contact</string>
    <string name="avoid_close_2">•\tAvoid close contact with people who are sick</string>
    <string name="put_distance">•\tPut distance between yourself and other people if COVID-19 is spreading in your community. This is especially important for people who are at higher risk of getting very sick.</string>
    <string name="steps_protect">Steps to protect others</string>
    <string name="home_if">Stay home if you’re sick</string>
    <string name="home_sick">•\tStay home if you are sick, except to get medical care. Learn what to do if you are sick.</string>
    <string name="cough_sneezes">Cover coughs and sneezes</string>
    <string name="mouth_and_nose">•\tCover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze or use the inside of your elbow.</string>
    <string name="throu_tissues">•\tThrow used tissues in the trash.</string>
    <string name="immediately">•\tImmediately wash your hands with soap and water for at least 20 seconds. If soap and water are not readily available, clean your hands with a hand sanitizer that contains at least 60% alcohol.</string>
    <string name="wear_face">Wear a facemask if you are sick</string>
    <string name="should_wear">•\tIf you are sick:  You should wear a facemask when you are around other people (e.g., sharing a room or vehicle) and before you enter a healthcare provider’s office. If you are not able to wear a facemask (for example, because it causes trouble breathing), then you should do your best to cover your coughs and sneezes, and people who are caring for you should wear a facemask if they enter your room. Learn what to do if you are sick.</string>
    <string name="not_sick">•\tIf you are NOT sick: You do not need to wear a facemask unless you are caring for someone who is sick (and they are not able to wear a facemask). Facemasks may be in short supply and they should be saved for caregivers.</string>
    <string name="clean_disinfect">Clean and disinfect</string>
    <string name="clean_and_disinfect_2">•\tClean AND disinfect frequently touched surfaces daily. This includes tables, doorknobs, light switches, countertops, handles, desks, phones, keyboards, toilets, faucets, and sinks.</string>
    <string name="surfaces_are_dirty">•\tIf surfaces are dirty, clean them: Use detergent or soap and water prior to disinfection.</string>
    <string name="Coronaviruses">Coronaviruses</string>
    <string name="corona_family">Coronaviruses are a family of viruses that cause illnesses ranging from the common cold to more severe diseases such as severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) and the Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS). These viruses were originally transmitted between animals and people. SARS, for instance, was transmitted from civet cats to humans while MERS moved to humans from a type of camel. Several known coronaviruses are circulating in animals that have not yet infected humans.</string>
    <string name="virus_originate">Where did the virus originate?</string>
    <string name="coronavirus_comes">The name coronavirus comes from the Latin word corona, meaning crown or halo. Under an electron microscope, the image of the virus looks like a solar corona.</string>
    <string name="novel_coronavirus">The novel coronavirus, identified by Chinese authorities on January 7 and since named COVID-19, is a new strain that had not been previously identified in humans. Little is known about it, although human-to-human transmission has been confirmed.</string>
    <string name="chines_health">Chinese health authorities are still trying to determine the origin of the virus, which they say likely came from a seafood market in Wuhan where wildlife was also traded illegally. On February 7, Chinese researchers said the virus could have spread from an infected animal species to humans through illegally-trafficked pangolins, which are prized in Asia for food and medicine.</string>
    <string name="scientists">Scientists have pointed to either bats or snakes as the source of the virus.</string>
    <string name="the_symptoms">What are the symptoms?</string>
    <string name="accourding_to_who">According to the WHO, signs of infection include fever, cough, shortness of breath and breathing difficulties. In more severe cases, it can lead to pneumonia, multiple organ failure and even death.</string>
    <string name="current_estimates">Current estimates of the incubation period - the amount of time between infection and the onset of symptoms - range from one to 14 days. Most infected people show symptoms within five to six days. However, infected patients can also be asymptomatic, meaning they do not display any symptoms despite having the virus in their systems.</string>
    <string name="how_deadly">How deadly is it?</string>
    <string name="with_more">With more than 4,200 recorded deaths, the number of fatalities from this new coronavirus has surpassed the toll of the 2002-2003 SARS outbreak, which also originated in China. SARS killed about 9 percent of those it infected - nearly 800 people worldwide and more than 300 in China alone. MERS, which did not spread as widely, was more deadly, killing one-third of those it infected.</string>
    <string name="while_new">While the new coronavirus is more widespread in China than SARS in terms of case numbers, the mortality rate remains considerably lower at approximately 2 percent, according to the WHO.</string>
    <string name="where_have_cases">Where have cases been reported?</string>
    <string name="most_cases">Most cases and deaths have been reported in China - the vast majority in Hubei province. Deaths have also been confirmed in Hong Kong, the Philippines, Japan, France, Taiwan, South Korea, Italy and Iran.</string>
    <string name="the_virus_has">The virus has spread to many countries in the Asia-Pacific region as well as in Europe, North America, the Middle East and Africa. The majority of cases outside China are among people who recently travelled to the country, however, instances of human-to-human transmission have been recorded in several countries and questions have been raised about cases with no apparent link to China.</string>
</resources>